topic: Java
deck: CS::Languages::Java
notes:
        -
                uuid: 2fc0dd24-e54c-44a6-8977-664f7ab19689
                front: 'Join `List<String>` by `", "`'
                back: '`list.stream().collect(Collectors.joining(", "))`'
                include_reverse: true
        -
                uuid: 8c37d746-1c07-4cfa-b9c9-14755ebad4c7
                front: 'Call map function on `List<String>` to convert to integers, then sum up results'
                back: '`list.stream().mapToLong(fn).sum()`'
                include_reverse: true
        -
                uuid: 6b9be4dc-6e46-46d0-af6c-53b8b9a0ac47
                front: 'Group `List<X>` by result of `fn`, yielding `Map<X, List<Y>>`'
                back: '`list.stream().collect(Collectors.groupingBy(fn))`'
                include_reverse: true
        -
                uuid: 265249d1-4e19-4179-a7ac-5d7ee2867724
                front: 'Convert from `List<X>` to `List<Y>` through `fn`'
                back: '`list.stream().map(fn).collect(Collectors.toList())`'
                include_reverse: true
        -
                uuid: 03204f7b-1349-47b1-acb5-16df12473405
                front: 'Class of pair / map entry'
                back: '`Map.Entry<K, V>`'
                include_reverse: true
        -
                uuid: e675da1d-7e79-4e4a-a1de-90df8795ff9f
                front: 'Get list sublist of items [5;10)'
                back: '`list.subList(5, 10);`'
                include_reverse: true
        -
                uuid: 3036df31-5a38-4640-a8ea-008dc66a6f5e
                front: 'Write stack trace of exception to stdout'
                back: '`exception.printStackTrace();`'
        -
                uuid: eb4f1c47-9dde-474a-9fdf-66af8365b389
                front: "Set `Set<T> s1` to the intersection of `s1` and `s2`"
                back: "`s1.retainAll(s2);`"
        -
                uuid: 7fe94df0-718d-4208-a861-f5363e130b34
                front: "Set `Set<T> s1` to the `s1` set-minus `s2`"
                back: "`s1.removeAll(s2);`"
        -
                uuid: c487c222-f2f3-4ecd-80b8-981d410197d0
                front: "Convert list to set using stream"
                back: "`list.stream().collect(Collectors.toSet())`"
